Guide to the General Frederick Steele Papers, 1845-1965 (inclusive), 1862-1868 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
- Series IA. Correspondence and papers of General Frederick Steele, 1845-1890.
  - Correspondence 1865, January 1-10. (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - 4. 1865, Jan. 3.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 2. Printed, s. Geo. L. Wilbur. District of Natchez, Davidson to command.
    - 5. 1865, Jan. 3.Division of West Mississippi - Office Assistant Inspector General. Printed circular No. 1. Re: reports.
    - 6. 1865, Jan. 3.Reserve Corps, Military Division of West Mississippi. AD. Report. Under orders to New Orleans.
    - 7. 1865, Jan. 3.3rd Brigade Reserve Corps. G.O. No. 1. Printed, s. Geo. Monroe. C. C. Andrews to command.
    - 8. 1865, Jan. 3.War Department - A.G.O. S.O. No. 2. Extract s. E. D. Townsend. Printed. Discharge of Wm. R. Moore.
    - 9. 1865, Jan. 4Reserve Corps, MDWM - Report of troops. AD. Docket s. C. T. Christensen.
    - 10. 1865, Jan. 4.3rd Brigade, Reserve Corps. G.O. No. 2. Printed, s. Geo. Monroe. Re: drills.
    - 11. 1865, Jan. 5.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 3. Printed. Monies from sales of seized properties, etc.
    - 12. 1865, Jan. 5.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 5. Printed extract s. C. T. Christensen. C. S. McEntee assigned to duty with FS, commanding U.S. Forces at Kennerville, La.
    - 13. 1865, Jan. 5.Chas. Thomas to E. R. S. Canby. Copy with NS of C. T. Christensen 1/29/65.Foraging system
    - 14. 1865, Jan. 6.C. T. Christensen to [Daniel] Ullmann. Tel. signed, copied for FS. Andrews to report to FS with 3rd Brigade, Reserve Corps.
    - 15. 1865, Jan. 6.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 6, extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. F. W. Emery to report to Andrews.
    - 16. 1865, Jan. 6.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 6, extract 6. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Lazelle to report to FS.
    - 17. 1865, Jan. 6.Division of West Mississippi - Office Chief of Artillery and Ordnance. Printed circular No. 1. Re: inspections and reports.
    - 18. 1865, Jan. 7.W. P. Coleman to FS. ALS. Ruin of Bellegrove Mansion, occupation, etc.
    - 19. 1865, Jan. 7.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 7., extract 6. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Atkinson to report of FS and McEntee.
    - 20. 1865, Jan. 7.2nd Maine Cavalry Veteran Volunteers. Roster of officers s. [J. Wm. Haight, Jr.].
    - 21. 1865, Jan. 7.3rd Brigade Reserve Corps. G.O. No. 3. Printed, s. Geo. Monroe. Camp orders.
    - 22. 1865, Jan. 7.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 1. Printed. B. F. Butler relieved of command.
    - 23. 1865, Jan. 7.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 2. Printed, s. F. W. Emery. Cost of clothing and equipage.
    - 24. 1865, Jan. 8.Elias S. Dennis to John F. Lacey. LS. Recommendations for orderlies and clerks.
    - 25. 1865, Jan. 8.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 4. Printed. Draft.
    - 26. 1865, Jan. 8.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 5. Printed. Exchanged prisoners.
    - 27. 1865, Jan. 8.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 8, extract 5. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. 83rd Ohio Volunteer Infantry.
    - 28. 1865, Jan. 8.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 8, extract 6. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. O. M. Humphrey to report to FS.
    - 29. 1865, Jan. 9.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 9, extract 1. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Brill discharge.
    - 30. 1865, Jan. 9.15th Massachusetts Battery. Roster of Commissioned Officers. DS of A. Rowse.
    - 31. 1865, Jan. 9.4th Battery Light Artillery, Massachusetts Veteran Volunteers. Roster of Commissioned Officers. [DS?] Geo. W. Taylor.
    - 32. 1865, Jan. 9.46 th Regiment Illinois Infantry Veteran Volunteers. DS of John J. Jones. Roster of Commissioned Officers.
    - 33. 1865, Jan. 9.M. K. Lawler to J. F. Lacey. LS. Suggestions. for orderlies.
    - 34. 1865, Jan. 9.30th Missouri Volunteer Infantry (Consolidated Organization). Roster of Commissioned Officers. DS of W. T. Wilkinson.
    - 35. 1865, Jan. 9.FS to Headquarters, Military Division of West Mississippi. NS on docket. 2 NSs of C. T. Christensen, 1/9 and 1/11 and ANS of C. G. Sawtelle 1/11. Re: Wood, fuel.
    - 36. 1865, Jan. 9.26th N. Y. Battery. ADS of Adam Beattie. Roster of Commissioned Officers.
    - 37. 1865, Jan. 10.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 10, extract 2. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Peebles discharge.
    - 38. 1865, Jan. 10.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 10, extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Gooding to report to FS.
    - 39. 1865, Jan. 10.Division of West Mississippi - Office Assistant Inspector General. Printed circular No. 2. Acting Assistant Inspectors General.
    - 40. 1865, Jan. 10.8th Regiment Illinois Veteran Volunteers. DS of Josiah A. Sheetz. Roster of Commissioned Officers.
    - 41. 1865, Jan. 10.U.S. Forces Kennerville, La. (FS's command). Tri-Monthly Consolidated Morning Report. Printed form filled in and s. John F. Lacey.
  - Correspondence 1865, January 11-15. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - 1. 1865, Jan. 11.A. D. Bailie to [FS]. ALS. Troops going to Kennerville.
    - 2. 1865, Jan. 11.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 11, extract 7. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Baker appointed Assistant Commissary of Musters.
    - 3. 1865, Jan. 11.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 11, extract 8. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharges.
    - 4. 1865, Jan. 11.Division of West Mississippi - Reserve Corps-Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular. DS of McEntee. Asks lists of Quarter Masters.
    - 5. 1865, Jan. 11.M. K. Lawler to Jno. F. Lacey. LS. Suggests Hunt as medical officer to 4th Massachusetts Battery. Docket: 1865/ Jan. 11. John F. Lacey to Humphrey. ANS. 1/16/65 Otis M. Humphrey to [Lacey?]. ANS.
    - 6. 1865, Jan. 11.A. Lockwood [Adams Express Co. of New Orleans] to [FS]. ALS. Introduction.
    - 7. 1865, Jan. 12. W. P. Coleman. ADS. Protest against reoccupation of his house and grounds. Docket: John F. Lacey to A. Rowse. ANS. 1/13/65. Orders abandonment of property. A. Rowse to [Lacey]. ANS. 1/15/65. Complies.
    - 8. 1865, Jan. 12. Levi Davis to C. T. Christensen. ALS. Asks that his Ambulance Corps be assigned to a Brigade of the Reserve Corps. Docket: 1/15/65 Referred to Humphrey by order of FS. ANS of John F. Lacey. 1/15/65. Otis M. Humphrey. ANS.
    - 9-12. 1865, Jan. 12. Elias S. Dennis to John F. Lacey. 4 LSs. Payroll, appointment, recommends, sends roster.
    - 13. 1865, Jan. 12. Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 12, extract 8. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Cross, leave of absence.
    - 14-15. 1865, Jan. 12. Division of West Mississippi - Reserve Corps - Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular. DS of McEntee. Daily forage report and copy.
    - 16. 1865, Jan. 12. Division of West Mississippi - Reserve Corps Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular. DS of McEntee. Forage.
    - 17. 1865, Jan. 12. 161st N.Y. Volunteers. DS of Wm. B. Kinsey. Roster of Commissioned Officers.
    - 18. 1865, Jan. 12. 20th Iowa Volunteer Infantry. DS of J. B. Leake. Roster of Commissioned Officers.
    - 19. 1865, Jan. 12.23rd Iowa Infantry Volunteers. DS of S. L. Glasgow. Roster of Commissioned Officers.
    - 20. 1865, Jan. 12.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 7. Printed. Limits of the Dept. of the South.
    - 21. 1865, Jan. 13.Charles Black to C. T. Christensen. LS. Asks that 99th Illinois Infantry be consolidated into 37th Illinois Infantry. Docket: 1/17/65 NS of FS--recommended. 3 notes in obliterated pencil by C.T.C. and 2 others.
    - 22. 1865, Jan. 13.99th Illinois Volunteers. Copy s. John F. Lacey. Roster of Commissioned Officers, enclosed in #21.
    - 23. 1865, Jan. 13.Charles Black to John F. Lacey. ANS. Request for circulars.
    - 24. 1865, Jan. 13.Charles Black to John F. Lacey. NS. Houston, Acting Assistant Inspector General of 4th Brigade.
    - 25. 1865, Jan. 13.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 13. extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Leave of absence.
    - 26. 1865, Jan. 13.Division of West Mississippi - Reserve Corps - Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular. DS of Chas. S. McEntee. Asks reports of horses, mules, wagons, etc.
    - 27. 1865, Jan. 13.Division of West Mississippi - Reserve Corps - Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular. DS of Chas. S. McEntee. Inspection of means of transportation.
    - 28. 1865, Jan. 13.M. K. Lawler to John F. Lacey. LS. Recommends a clerk.
    - 29. 1865, Jan. 13.M. K. Lawler to John F. Lacey. LS. Hancock, Acting Assistant Inspector General, 1st Brigade.
    - 30. 1865, Jan. 13.J. W. Moore to John F. Lacey. ANS. Forwarding lists.
    - 31. 1865, Jan. 13.U.S. Forces - Kenner, La. Circular No. 1. DS of John F. Lacey. Requisitions for Quarter Master supplies.
    - 32. 1865, Jan. 14.J. L. Baker to J. F. Lacey. ALS. Requests F. H. W. French as clerk.
    - 33. 1865, Jan. 14.C. T. Christensen to S. A. Hurlbut. Copy to FS, s. C. T. Christensen. Railroad guard from New Orleans to be replaced by FS's troops.
    - 34. 1865, Jan. 14.Levi Davis to [J. F. Lacey]. ALS. Disposition of his ambulance corps.
    - 35. 1865, Jan. 14.Dept. of the Gulf - Acting Assistant Quarter Master. Printed and ms. document s. E. M. Wiswell. List of books sent.
    - 36. 1865, Jan. 14.Dept. of the Gulf - Acting Assistant Quarter Master to J. F. Lacey. Printed and ms. document s. E. M. Wiswell. List of forms sent.
    - 37. 1865, Jan. 14.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 6. Printed. Court martial of Isaac H. Walker.
    - 38. 1865, Jan. 14.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 14, extract 2. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Leave of absence for Dyer.
    - 39. 1865, Jan. 14.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 14, extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Emery reassigned.
    - 40. 1865, Jan. 14.4th Brigade - Reserve Corps - Office Senior Surgeon. Printed and ms. document s. O. Peabody. Consolidated weekly report of sick and wounded. Docket: 1/18/65 NS of Otis M. Humphrey.
    - 41. 1865, Jan. 14.W. W. Storer to [FS]. ALS. Arrival of command at Morganza.
    - 42. 1865, Jan. 14.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 3. Printed. Joint Congressional resolution thanking Sherman.
    - 43. 1865, Jan. 15.J. L. Baker to John F. Lacey. ANS. Re: Pvt. French.
    - 44. 1865, Jan. 15.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 15, extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Leave of absence for Gibbs.
    - 45. 1865, Jan. 15.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 15, extract 6. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Trull assigned to court martial detail.
    - 46. 1865, Jan. 15.Otis M. Humphrey to FS. ALS. Requests detail of a Capt. as Chief Ambulance Officer.
    - 47. 1865, Jan. 15.U.S. Forces - Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. Circular No. 1. DS of Otis M. Humphries. Location regulations
    - 48-49. 1865, Jan. 15.J. B. Wheeler to FS. ALS. Personal, FS's career, Arkansas, etc. Enclosure: clipping from Rochester Union by Foster.
  - Correspondence 1865, January 16-20. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - 1-2. 1865, Jan. 16.C. C. Andrews to John F. Lacey. LS and DS. Covering letter and Roster of Commissioned Officers of 3rd Brigade, Reserve Corps 1/15/65.
    - 3. 1865, Jan. 16.Dept. of the Gulf. S.O. No. 16, extract 7. Printed, s. C. S. Sargent. 24th Indiana Volunteers relieved of duty in Defences of New Orleans, to report to FS.
    - 4. 1865, Jan. 16.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 16, extract 1. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Leave of absence.
    - 5. 1865, Jan. 16.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 16, extract 4. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of Geo. Marion.
    - 6. 1865, Jan. 16.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 16, extract 4 [sic]. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of Alex. S. Millard.
    - 7. 1865, Jan. 16.M. K. Lawler to C. T. Christensen. LS. Recommends consolidating 34th Illinois Infantry with another Illinois Regiment and retaining Black.
    - 8. 1865, Jan. 16.Chas. S. McEntee to J. F. Lacey. LS. Applies for detail for guard duty at Quarter Master depot.
    - 9. 1865, Jan. 16.Timothy Owen to [J. F. Lacey]. Letter s. by clerk. Horses.
    - 10. 1865, Jan. 16.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. S.O. No. 1. DS of Otis M. Humphrey. Re: Hipolite.
    - 11. 1865, Jan. 16.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. S.O. No. 2. DS of Otis M. Humphrey. Asks for reports.
    - 12. 1865, Jan. 16.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 4. Printed. Mourning for Edward Everett.
    - 13. 1865, Jan. 17.C. T. Christensen to FS. Tel., copy. Railroad track blocked by wood.
    - 14. 1865, Jan. 17.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 7 Printed. Interference with means of transportation.
    - 15. 1865, Jan. 17.Division of West Mississippi, Reserve Corps-Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular. DS of Chas S. McEntee. Train Kennerville-New Orleans.
    - 16. 1865, Jan. 17.82nd U.S. Colored Infantry. Roster of Officers. DS of J. Wm. Haight, Jr.
    - 17. 1865, Jan. 17.1st Florida Cavalry. Roster of Commissioned Officers. DS of J. Wm. Haight, Jr.
    - 18. 1865, Jan. 17.Otis M. Humphrey to FS. LS. Recommends organization of ambulance corps according to General Code No. 38 with modifications.
    - 19. 1865, Jan. 17.[U.S. Forces], Kenner, La. - Board of Survey. ADS of Samuel Wagenhals. Commissary stores. Docket: 1/18/65 ANS of John H. Kelly, NS of C. C. Andrews and ANS of John F. Lacey.
    - 20. 1865, Jan. 17.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. S.O. No. 2. DS of Otis M. Humphrey. Examining board.
    - 21. 1865, Jan. 17.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 5. Printed. Dept. of Ohio combined with Cumberland under Thomas.
    - 22. 1865, Jan. 17.E. I. Wage to J. F. Lacey. LS. Re: levee, Parish of Jefferson.
    - 23. 1865, Jan. 18.Charles Black to C. T. Christensen. ALS. Recommends as partial basis of reorganization proposed in request of 13th.
    - 24. 1865, Jan. 18.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 8. Printed. General court martial.
    - 25. 1865, Jan. 18.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 18, extract 1. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Clerks with Chief Mustering Officer.
    - 26. 1865, Jan. 18.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 18, extract 2. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen Discharge of Roberts.
    - 27. 1865, Jan. 18.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 18, extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of Jas. A. Peter.
    - 28. 1865, Jan. 18.86th U.S. Colored Infantry. Roster of Officers. Copy s. J. Wm. Haight, Jr.
    - 29-30. 1865, Jan. 18.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Board of Survey. [for Lt. A. Rowse, 15th Massachusetts Battery]. Proceedings, 2 copies, both in several hands. Deficiencies in Quarter Master stores, etc. Signatures of Chas W. Williams, Geo. N. Jenkins and Alex. S. Millard. Docket: ANS of John F. Lacey 1/24/65; on 2nd copy NS of Lacey.
    - 31. 1865, Jan. 18.Thomas M. Vincent to Commanding General, Division of West Mississippi. Official copy forwarded with ANS of C. T. Christensen to FS. 1/18/65. Recruiting for Cavalry and Artillery.
    - 32. 1865, Jan. 18.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 6. Printed. Release of prisoners from cells and irons.
    - 33. 1865, Jan. 18.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 8. Printed. Acting assistant surgeons.
    - 34. 1865, Jan. 19.Elias S. Dennis to John F. Lacey. LS. Condition of levees.
    - 35. 1865, Jan. 19.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 9. Printed. Repair of small arms.
    - 36. 1865, Jan. 19.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 19, extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of J. E. Smith.
    - 37. 1865, Jan. 19.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 19, extract 4. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of B. Freeman.
    - 38. 1865, Jan. 19.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 19, extract 5. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of W. Wightman.
    - 39. 1865, Jan. 19.1st Brigade, Reserve Corps, MDWM. S.O. No. 7, extract 2, s. John J. Huntley. Curtis detailed as acting Ordnance Officer.
    - 40. 1865, Jan. 19.3rd Brigade, Reserve Corps, MDWM. G.O. No. 4. Printed, s. George Monroe. Discipline.
    - 41. 1865, Jan. 20.Charles Black to John F. Lacey. LS. Inspection of levee.
    - 42. 1865, Jan. 20.Jas. H. Coates to W. A. [sic] Kuhn. [W.E.] ALS. Cases of enlisted men in 11th Illinois Infantry under arrest and awaiting sentence. Docket: ANS of Elias S. Dennis and 3 separate dockets 1/21 NS of J. F. Lacey, 1/23 ANS of Jas. H. Coates, 1/23 ANS of Elias S. Dennis.
    - 43. 1865, Jan. 20.James H. B. Henry to Geo. S. Atkinson. ALS. Introduction. Docket: NS Geo. S. Atkinson to Lacey. 1/20/65.
    - 44. 1865, Jan. 20.M. K. Lawler to Jno. F. Lacey. LS.
    - 45. 1865, Jan. 20.W. E. Kuhn to John F. Lacey. ALS. Transmittal.
    - 46. 1865, Jan. 20.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. -Tri-monthly Morning Report. Printed and ms. document s. F. Steele.
    - 47. 1865, Jan. 20.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. ADS of John F. Lacey. Abstract of tri-monthly return.
    - 48. 1865, Jan. 20.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. S.O. No. 3. DS of Otis M. Humphrey. Orders re: a hospital steward.
    - 49. 1865, Jan. 20.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 9. Printed. Territory of Arizona re-annexed to Dept. of the Pacific under McDowell.
  - Correspondence 1865, January 21-27. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - 1. 1865, Jan. 21.Charles Black to John F. Lacey. LS Transmittal.
    - 2. 1865, Jan. 21.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 21, extract 2. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Transfer of wounded soldier.
    - 3. 1865, Jan. 21.Charles S. McEntee to J. F. Lacey. LS. Requests J. B. Waters as mounted orderly.
    - 4. 1865, Jan. 21.Geo. A. Mitchell to FS. LS. Sokalski's pay accounts.
    - 5. 1865, Jan. 22.Theo. R. Crandell to C. T. Christensen. [A?]LS. Asks for a decision in AWOL case. Docket: 1/24/65 ANS of G. W. Clark and NS of C.C. Andrews
    - 6. 1865, Jan. 22.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 10. Printed. Dishonorable discharge of A. Forrer.
    - 7. 1865, Jan. 22.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 11. Printed. General court martial of Franzisko B. John.
    - 8-9. 1865, Jan. 22.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 22, extract 2. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Leaves of absence.
    - 10. 1865, Jan. 22.W. S. Hatch to [FS]. [ANS or tel.?]. Announces expected arrival.
    - 11. 1865, Jan. 22.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. Circular No. 3. DS of Otis M. Humphrey. Returns of medical officers.
    - 12. 1865, Jan. 23.C. T. Christensen to C. C. Andrews. ALS (Copy). Directs Andrews to Lakeport, etc. and to report to Gen. Granger.
    - 13. 1865, Jan. 23.C. T. Christensen to FS. ADfS. 3rd Brigade to go to Pensacola, remainder to E. Pascagoula.
    - 14. 1865, Jan. 23.C. T. Christensen to FS. ALS. Transmits instructions for disposition of 83rd Ohio Volunteer Infantry.
    - 15. 1865, Jan. 23.Division of West Mississippi, Reserve Corps, Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular. DS of Chas.S. McEntee. Estimates for clothing, etc.
    - 16. 1865, Jan. 23.John P. Hawkins to FS. ALS. Re: Morgan L. Smith, requests be assigned to a Division command with FS. ANS of C. T. Christensen--Canby will comply if FS wants. The Brigadiers you have now have not stuff enough to make good Division Commanders.
    - 17. 1865, Jan. 23.John H. Kelly to George Monroe. ALS. Represents enlisted men, request to rejoin Regiment. Docket: 1/23 NS of C. C. Andrews, 1/24 NS of John F. Lacey, 1/24 ANS of Richard A. King for M. K. Lawler.
    - 18. 1865, Jan. 23.C. G. Seawell to FS. ALS. Steamer ready to take troops to Pensacola.
    - 19. 1865, Jan. 24.C. C. Andrews to C. T. Christensen. Copy s. George Monroe. Arrival at Kenner, transportation not at hand.
    - 20. 1865, Jan. 24.C. T. Christensen to FS. [ALS or tel.?]. Order 24th Indiana to embark for Pensacola.
    - 21. 1865, Jan. 24.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 24, extract 2. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharges Somers.
    - 22. 1865, Jan. 24.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 24, extract 6. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Resignation of L. L. Whitney.
    - 23. 1865, Jan. 24.83rd Regiment Ohio Volunteer Infantry. Copy of document s. J. Wm. Haight, Jr. Roster of Commissioned Officers.
    - 24. 1865, Jan. 24.John F. Lacey to C. C. Andrews. ALS. A misunderstanding re: orders. Docket: 1/24 ANS of C. C. Andrews. reply.
    - 25. 1865, Jan. 24.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. S.O. No. 4. DS of Otis M. Humphrey.
    - 26. 1865, Jan. 25.District of West Florida. G.O. No. 6. Printed. Repeats G.O. No. 1. Organization of troops.
    - 27. 1865, Jan. 25.District of West Florida. G.O. No. 7. Printed. Troop organization.
    - 28. 1865, Jan. 25.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 25, extract 5. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of W. P. Mitchell.
    - 29. 1865, Jan.25.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 25, extract 9. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Resignation of Wm. D. Crooke.
    - 30. 1865, Jan. 26.C. T. Christensen to John F. Lacey. Tel. Andrews to be dropped from returns, general courts martial can be convened by FS's orders only.
    - 31. 1865, Jan. 26.Division of West Mississippi. G.O. No. 12. Printed. War Dept. S.O. No. 10, extract 8. Dishonorable discharge of R. L. Orr.
    - 32. 1865, Jan. 26.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 26, extract 1. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Resignation of Wm. A. Greene.
    - 33. 1865, Jan. 26.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 26, extract 4. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. On recommend of [FS] 28th Illinois Veteran Volunteer Infantry to form 2 more companies.
    - 34. 1865, Jan. 26.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 26, extract 5. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Discharge of G. G. Moser.
    - 35. 1865, Jan. 26.War Department - A.G.O. G.O. No. 10. Printed. Congressional resolution--thanks A. H. Terry.
    - 36. 1865, Jan. 27.District of West Florida. G.O. No. 8. Printed. Duties of E. Hutchinson and H. K. Southwick.
    - 37. 1865, Jan. 27.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 27, extract 2. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Transfer of 2nd Illinois Artillery.
    - 38. 1865, Jan. 27.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 27, extract 3. Printed, s. C. T. Christensen. Batteries of Light Art. to report to FS.
    - 39. 1865, Jan. 27.A. C. Matthews to C. T. Christensen. LS. Statement re: consolidation.
    - 40. 1865, Jan. 27.Jas. Totten to C. T. Christensen. LS. Reports Regiments which have failed to furnish reports. Docket: 1/30 NS of Alfred Fredberg.
    - 41. 1865, Jan. 27.Jas. Totten to FS. Tel. Transportation.
    - 42. 1865, Jan. 27.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. G.O. No._____. Df., fragment. H. W. Hart, Inspector and Assistant Chief Medical Officer.
    - 43. 1865, Jan. 27.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. Circular No. 4. DS of Otis M. Humphrey. Hospitals, etc.
    - 44. 1865, Jan. 27.U.S. Forces, Kenner, La. - Chief Medical Officer. Extract of Circular No. 4 (IV) s. John. F. Lacey. H. W. Hart appointment.
    - 45. 1865, Jan. 27.[U.S. Forces, Kenner, La.], Reserve Corps - Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular s. Chas. S. McEntee. Request for forms.
    - 46. 1865, Jan. 27.[U.S. Forces, Kenner, La.], Reserve Corps - Office Chief Quarter Master. Circular s. Chas. S. McEntee. Instructions re: reports.
  - Correspondence 1865, January 28-31. (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - 1. 1865, Jan. 28.Geo. S. Atkinson to J. F. Lacey. LS.
    - 2. 1865, Jan. 28D. P. Ballard to John F. Lacey. ALS. Asks for an issue of orders re: Assistant Quarter Masters and detailing of men for his office. Approval s. Otis M. Humphrey.
    - 3. 1865, Jan. 28.Charles Black to John F. Lacey. ALS. Re: consolidation.
    - 4. 1865, Jan. 28.Division of West Mississippi. S.O. No. 28, extract 5. Printed, s. Geo. L. Wilbur. Re: Capt. T. Pearson, fraud charge.
    - 5. 1865, Jan. 28.Division of West Mississippi - Office Chief of Artillery and Ordnance. Printed circular No. 3, s. Wm. Hunt, Jr. Forms for reporting.
    - 6. 1865, Jan. 28.Lawrence Jacoby to FS. ALS. Reporting for duty.